<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:backgroundTint="@color/bg"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context=".MainActivity">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_gravity="center"
        android:layout_marginTop="15dp"
        android:fontFamily="sans-serif-condensed-medium"
        android:gravity="center"
        android:text="About Me!"
        android:textSize="30sp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="200dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        app:srcCompat="@drawable/pics" />


    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="150dp">


        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/textView"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="150dp"
            android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
            android:padding="20dp"
            android:text="ðŸ‘‹ Hello, world! I'm Sanjay Mali, and I'm on a mission to bring digital dreams to life as a frontend developer. ðŸŒŸ
ðŸŒ† From my early days, I've been captivated by the intersection of technology and creativity. My story began when I first tinkered with HTML and CSS to craft my very first website. Little did I know that this fascination would ignite a lifelong passion for web development.ðŸ”—
ðŸ› ï¸ Over the years, I've honed my skills, diving deep into the intricacies of JavaScript, mastering responsive design, and exploring the vast world of frontend frameworks like React, Node.js and Bootstrap . Each line of code I write is infused with the commitment to delivering not just functional, but also visually stunning digital experiences.ðŸ”±
ðŸ” I'm not only focused on the technical aspects of my work but also on user behavior. Adept at analyzing user journeys and feedback, I refine and optimize applications to provide a seamless and engaging experience.ðŸŒ
ðŸŒŸ I'm currently on the lookout for my next adventure. Whether it's collaborating on innovative projects or joining a dynamic team, I'm eager to contribute my skills and passion to create exceptional digital experiences.ðŸŒŸ
ðŸ’¬ If you're as passionate about the frontend as I am, let's connect and explore opportunities together. You can reach out to me here on LinkedIn or at sanjaymali94284@gmail.com. Together, let's continue this exciting journey of turning lines of code into digital art.ðŸš€
GitHub :- github.com/sanjay-mali
LinkedIn :- linkedin.com/in/sanjay-mali-63672a21a
Twitter :- x.com/BoltHacker1
Email :- sanjaymali94284@gmail.com" />

    </ScrollView>

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
        android:orientation="horizontal">


        <Button
            android:id="@+id/github"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:backgroundTint="@color/btnColor"
            android:text="Github" />

        <Button
            android:id="@+id/linkdin"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_weight="1"
            android:backgroundTint="@color/btnColor"
            android:text="Linkdin" />
    </LinearLayout>


</LinearLayout>